<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My blog</title><link>https://msdlr.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on My blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://msdlr.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 months in, a retrospective</title><link>https://msdlr.github.io/blog/posts/three-months-in/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://msdlr.github.io/blog/posts/three-months-in/</guid><description>So, it&amp;rsquo;s finally been 3 months since I started this thing. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working very hard on reseaching, developing, and finally solidify a paper based on my work.
I feel like the paper distracted my too much about the development of future potential features. I know that papers are a gateway to getting your PhD culminated, but I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel that it should be an outcome of your day-to-day job that just happens in a more organic way.</description></item><item><title>Starting out</title><link>https://msdlr.github.io/blog/posts/starting-out/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://msdlr.github.io/blog/posts/starting-out/</guid><description>Well, not really Well, this is my first post here, now that I got a little free time and decided to write something. Now that Github Actions can generate the post pages automatically once I push a commit, the only thing that discourages me from posting is my own laziness.
Although this is my first post and I still officially have to submit all the paperwork to actually be a PhD student, I have to admit that I have been doing work for my thesis for a time now.</description></item><item><title>whoami</title><link>https://msdlr.github.io/blog/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://msdlr.github.io/blog/about/</guid><description>Hello there!
I am Miguel, a PhD student and research assistant at University of Castilla-La Mancha in Albacete, Spain. I made this blog to test out Hugo as a static site generator and share some stuff throughout my career.
I have done research about topics related to blockchain, traffic modelling, and I am now working in Quality of Service and power consumption, involved in the RED-SEA project.</description></item></channel></rss>